Anyone who mistreats
Hong Il-tak
or calls him a girl
is dead
Let's stop the crap
between guys
Especially you
Kim Hyeong-ju
Hey, Hyeong-ju
-Hyeon-wu
-What?
You got a problem
with that?
A lot has changed
after that day
No one's bothered me
for a week
Brute strength
really is the best
Usually, there are
a few jerks around
Lee Hyeon-wu
got rid of them for me
I feel at ease
Ugh, seriously
What is up with him?
This is so awkward
He smiled
Yes, that's
the biggest problem
I think Lee Hyeon-wu
likes me
Even though I'm a guy
That's why
he defended me
Anyone who mistreats
Hong Il-tak
or calls him a girl
is dead
I need to walk
a fine line
so he doesn't
get more serious
Il-tak
What are you doing
after school?
Here it is
I'd think he wants
to hang out
but is this b******
actually…
We get out
an hour early today
Wanna hang out?
Don't tell me…
Is he asking me out?
Please don't smile
like that